module.exports = [
  {
    question: "What is Greendale Community College's Mascot?",
    a: 'Greendale Racoon',
    b: 'Greendale Sandwich Artist',
    c: 'An anthropomorphized book',
    d: 'Greendale Human Being',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: "What is Senor Chang's nickname?",
    a: 'El Tigre',
    b: 'Changarang',
    c: 'El Cabra',
    d: 'Hefe Chang',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does Troy name his pet monkey?',
    a: 'Monkey',
    b: "Annie's boobs",
    c: 'Generalissimo',
    d: "Troy's monkey",
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: "What was Annie's dungeons and dragons character name?",
    a: 'Zippideedoo',
    b: 'Marrrrrrrr',
    c: 'Hector the Well Endowed',
    d: 'Bing Bong the Archer',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: "What company does Britta's short-lived corpo-humanoid boyfriend represent?",
    a: 'Subway',
    b: "Domino's",
    c: "Quizno's",
    d: 'Dr Pepper',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: "Pierce's racist dad's wig is made from this material",
    a: "an albino person's hair",
    b: 'Ivory',
    c: '100% wolf hair',
    d: 'Gold',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What animal does the Dean have an unhealthy obsession with?',
    a: 'Dalmations',
    b: 'Ferrets',
    c: 'Sugar gliders',
    d: 'Elephants',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What character did Pierce dress up as for the first halloween party?',
    a: 'Gordon Gekko',
    b: 'Sinbad (the pirate)',
    c: 'He-man',
    d: 'Beastmaster',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What feature is indicative of a character being from the "Darkest Timeline"',
    a: 'a monocle and fedora',
    b: 'a english accent',
    c: 'a felt goatee',
    d: 'a jacket made of question marks',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Troy's hero?"
    a: 'Carl Weathers',
    b: 'Ernie Hudson',
    c: 'Mekhi Phifer',
    d: 'LeVar Burton',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];